<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PI-osisoft on RVR</title>
    <link>https://rvillalongar.github.io/portafolio/tags/pi-osisoft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PI-osisoft on RVR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 08:00:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rvillalongar.github.io/portafolio/tags/pi-osisoft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Online Status of the Generation Assets on Android &amp; Apple</title>
      <link>https://rvillalongar.github.io/portafolio/post/projectbi_appmonitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 08:00:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rvillalongar.github.io/portafolio/post/projectbi_appmonitoring/</guid>
      <description>In the process of monitoring thermal generation, we had the need to centralize the information on news and criticalities for generation plants in Latin America. To solve this, we reuse a BI infrastructure plus the real-time information from the PI Osisoft platform, along with other management systems. The unification of this information was through an API. Later we develop (externally) the Android and Apple applications. With this we had all our clients in Latin America updated on the status of the generation and its criticalities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use case PrISM Implementation</title>
      <link>https://rvillalongar.github.io/portafolio/post/project05/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 08:00:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rvillalongar.github.io/portafolio/post/project05/</guid>
      <description>In search of a global tool for building algorithms focused on reducing unavailability. We developed a success case with the schneider team, which involved presenting a real unavailability, modeling the algorithm and understanding when we would have obtained an alarm to prevent unavailability on water pump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WareHouse Business intelligence on Process Data</title>
      <link>https://rvillalongar.github.io/portafolio/post/projectbi_warehouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 08:00:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rvillalongar.github.io/portafolio/post/projectbi_warehouse/</guid>
      <description>Within the need to monitor operational efficiency, we had the need to implement metrics corresponding to generation monitoring, with different levels of openings and dimensions. For this I had the opportunity to develop a Warehouse (from 0) containing operational data from Plant Information Osisoft (time series values) and other management systems (management or operational values). This project became the backbone of operational management, analysis and reporting for Latin America.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apply Similarity-Based Modeling to monitoring assets</title>
      <link>https://rvillalongar.github.io/portafolio/post/project04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 08:00:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rvillalongar.github.io/portafolio/post/project04/</guid>
      <description>#Tengo que decir que participe en la construccion y la aplicacion
With the University of Chile(Dr Marcos Orchard), Enel staff (leader Rodrigo Paredes) and Contact Engineers. We implement more advanced algorithms in real time platforms, together with the design of a framework for training new solutions or processes.
&amp;ldquo;Paper&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analysis Optimal condenser operation</title>
      <link>https://rvillalongar.github.io/portafolio/post/project03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2008 08:00:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rvillalongar.github.io/portafolio/post/project03/</guid>
      <description>The algorithm aims to monitor the thermal load that affects the condenser. Due to a bad operation, which the action is carried out by the plant operator, whether considering the impact on unavailability or efficiency</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Pump behavior</title>
      <link>https://rvillalongar.github.io/portafolio/post/project02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2008 08:00:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rvillalongar.github.io/portafolio/post/project02/</guid>
      <description>This application solves the non-existence of feedback on the position of the feed water valves of the AP, MP and BP DOMES in the control system. Based on this need, the behavior of each valve was modeled, allowing the modeled position to be compared with the position indicated by the control system setpoint. When a deviation over 5% occurs, the problem should be reviewed</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blade Path Temperature Anomalies Detection</title>
      <link>https://rvillalongar.github.io/portafolio/post/project01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rvillalongar.github.io/portafolio/post/project01/</guid>
      <description>algorithms that detect temperature deviations in the combustion chambers, comparing said deviations with a relational model of power and compressor outlet temperature, which allows detecting possible flaws in the combustion chambers. The objective of this system is to alert before the fault occurs or the alarm of the control system is activated.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
